(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
(Get ready, dig your anger up, MOB!)
(Get ready!)
Coming down,
could you fill your satisfaction?
You're a MOB.
Can't you feel your own frustration?
Coming down,
could you fill your satisfaction?
You're a MOB.
What do you want to be?
Wear your overflowing emotions
on your sleeve and break it down
What do you see once you go
beyond your limits?
(99.9! 99.9)
The mysterious percentage
Cr yin' my life, or yin' my psyche,
Cr yin' my heart in such commonplaces!
Is that your ideal? Is that your mind?
It all begins when it hits 100
The MOB is alive. The MOB is high.
The MOB is staying frustrated, aren't you?
Is that your ideal?
Is that your mind? Right now
YOUR LIFE IS YOUR OWN.
(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
"Mob Psycho 100 II"
(Get ready, dig your anger up, MOB!)
(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
(Get ready!)
"Boss Fight
- The Final Light~"
Now I'll be able to hit
you with everything...
My powers... and my rage.
"Output 20%"
Is that it?
This is finally getting interesting.
You're...
You're enjoying this, too, aren't you?
What the hell is going on?
They're fighting in
a whole different stratosphere!
As righteous as you try to sound,
deep down, you're the same as me.
Nii-san!
How does it feel to be released
from your shackles?
We are freer than anyone else!
Nii-san...
How... How could I...
How could I be so foolish?
It may have only been for a moment,
but I let this power control me!
You're so emotionally unstable.
At this rate, you'll never catch up to me,
no matter how far you go.
I am the best in the world!
How did your life end up being so hollow?
I can't judge you for the life
you chose, though.
You were just unlucky.
What are you talking about?
There is no one in this world
that is as lucky as me!
"Output 50%"
Heaven bestowed these powers upon me
and made you all extras,
created solely to make my star shine!
Really? Then it wasn't luck
that you were lacking.
It was bonds.
What?
You were the only one
who existed in your world.
You lived in overwhelming solitude.
I know that feeling well...
Living in a world where I'm completely alone,
one I want to forget forever.
I don't understand.
Why?
Why are you crying?
You might not believe me,
but I really don't want to hurt you.
I'm sorry...
What the hell is going on?
Don't ask me.
The president's aura is gone.
Does that mean it's over?
Yes!
Impressive. Is that boy actually human?
He's just a normal middle school kid.
Nii-san... You used a tremendous
amount of power again.
It's not over yet.
My dad's aura didn't disappear.
It changed.
My dad mentioned before that
he picked up the habit of only awakening
when put under a lot of stress.
This goes beyond human understanding.
How can one man's powers be so immense?
Shigeo... This is the one day in your life
you shouldn't try to do the impossible.
He's already using way more power
than he did when he beat me.
If you can't win, run.
You're not responsible for any of this,
Mob.
I've never felt like this before.
Wake up.
Don't think I'm going to let you say
you're done already.
Wake up!
No.
As much as I hate to admit it,
I'm not strong enough.
I don't have the power
to show you a new path.
You awakened my destructive impulses,
now you have to deal with them!
Don't go hiding in your shell now!
I give up.
I hoped that you could turn over a new leaf
and become a better person...
...but that hope's gone now!
I-It appears... that we're both...
...influencing each other quite a bit...
Yes. But I couldn't be a good influence.
I'm done. We can both lose at this point.
"Output 100%"
This is...
I might actually die...
Mob!
Shigeo.
--Nii-san!
--Heya.
Well done.
No, this is nothing.
Nothing compared to the fear
of losing all I have.
Body improvement! Fight on!
I'll defeat you!
If something like that makes it outside...
It'll explode...
It'll explode?
Oh, it'll explode!
Run away! Everyone, run away!
--Mob!
--You're alive!
He ended up releasing too much
energy and self-destructed!
You're bleeding like crazy!
Master, please run!
All that's left is an
excessive amount of energy.
I'm pretty sure an explosion will happen,
a huge one at that!
So you're saying we won't
be able to contain it.
Let's hurry!
Ritsu.
Let's run. We're gonna get caught
up in that if we stay here.
That's the president's final light...
Our president who was trying
to take over the world...
Just shut up and run! You're gonna die!
Huh? Hey, where's Shigeo?
You made the right choice.
There's no way to avoid this.
Your only choice is to end my life--
to sever the energy source--
Before the explosion happens.
What are you doing?
I'm going to contain the explosion.
In the end, you aren't able to defeat me,
save your friends, or save yourself.
With your powers, you should've
been able to handle this better.
Just having powers doesn't mean
everything works out for you.
But that's perfectly fine...
...as long as you make
the important choices yourself.
I'm the protagonist of my own life.
That's why I chose to be here.
No matter how much I dislike you,
to leave you to suffer on your own
would just be too sad.
So I'm going to help you.
What do you plan to do with that filthy cat?
Well, the poor thing was drenched
and shivering in the rain.
And think about it...
Sho will grow up into a gentle boy.
He's going to grow up watching you, after all.
We need to be gentle. Gentle.
Why did you have to be so violent?!
To lead an organization,
I need to establish my dominance.
You can't move people's hearts
with psychic powers!
No, power is absolute.
As long as I have this power,
people will follow me.
You think that's true for everyone?
I do.
Sho is also showing interest
in my powers as well.
Goodbye.
When did I...
If I can absorb it...
Don't. You'll just end up...
You wanted to apologize, didn't you?!
Then you need to say it loud and clear!
That's right. I also...
I also have someone I need
to express my feelings to!
Mob...
"Mob Psycho 100 II"
Nii-san!
Hey, wake up!
Kageyama-kun!
--Mob!
--Shigeo!
Nii-san!
He's regained consciousness.
Let's dig him out.
Thank goodness you're okay.
Unbelievable.
Anyway, we should get away from here.
Can you walk?
Yes...
All of our wounds have been healed.
Our clothes are in shambles, though.
You're right...
Shigeo, what's up with
the left side of your chest?
That's quite the bold fashion statement.
Seriously... You never cease to amaze.
I do consider you my rival, you know?
Don't wander off too far.
This ground... It's not concrete.
My mind feels all spacey.
The sky seems cramped.
Where are we?
There's the exit. Watch out for
things that may fall onto your head.
It's quiet.
Surprisingly, there aren't any
news helicopters flying around.
Well, yeah.
They're too scared to come here
when they know so little.
Everything seems fine,
even after that giant explosion.
What's going on?
I seriously thought
you were a goner back there.
I was sure ground zero
would've been eviscerated.
The hell is that?
But what appeared there happened to be...
Hey!
Nii-san! Are you okay?
Are you still actually hurt somewhere?
Thanks, Ritsu. I think my body's okay.
But lately, whenever I use a lot of power,
I have a hard time staying awake afterward.
Huh?
I'll carry you partway,
SO you can rest.
Carry him where? Our house is...
Sorry, he'll fix up your house,
but he'll need three days.
Just three days?!
You guys wanna come to my place?
It'll be a bit cramped,
but I'm sure we can make it work.
At least try to hide your displeasure, jeez.
Oh, don't worry about me.
Could we stop by the school first?
At this hour?
There should be a spare
tracksuit in his club room.
"Telepathy Club"
"Body Improvement Club"
That must be it.
I wonder if I could borrow one for myself.
"Lower body strengthening month!!" I
wonder if I could borrow one for myself.
"Lower body
strengthening month!!"
"Lower body strengthening month!!"
But I can't do it without asking...
"Lower body
strengthening month!!"
Tracksuit thieves!
Captain.
My heart just stopped!
I see.
I came here to get some dumbbells,
and you sure gave me a scare.
Sorry... You scared us pretty good, too.
I understand the situation now.
Hang on one second.
Hello? You see...
Um... Why's everyone from
the Body Improvement Club here?
We're about to...
The Body Improvement Club
will now begin a three-day four-night
strengthening hell training camp!
No, we're--
We should always help
each other out when in need!
I mean, we're really tired--
I'm sure you want to sleep on a giant futon!
No, a small one will do just fine!
We have enough room for all
of you at my granny's house!
You have to procure and make your own food,
so it'll be excellent training!
And it's just a 90-minute jog away!
We'll be there in no time!
Now, let's go!
R-Reigen-san, help...
Hey, that's great. Do your best.
I'm gonna take a cab home.
Body Improvement!
Fight on! Fight on!
How cruel...
I totally forgot!
I should've just gone over
to Reigen-san's place.
I wonder what that thing is.
It's even more confusing up close.
How does one of these things even grow?
Isn't it obvious?!
Aliens! This is the work of aliens!
--Amazing.
--Could this be...
...the work of our beloved leader?
Wow... It looks like a vegetable.
I bet Mob-kun was involved.
I just know it.
That's amazing!
You're the ones behind that giant plant?
W-Well...
If you're asking if we were
directly involved, then no.
--We basically were, though.
--What?
Amazing! Fantastic!
Mitsuura-san.
I think I'm going to stop coming here.
Kurosaki-san? But why?!
If everything goes well with your research
and you actually develop the technology
to make espers out of people,
we might get more espers
who misuse their powers.
So I think you should just stop.
I don't even need the money.
I agree.
We're actually not that impressive.
Kids...
All right!
I'll stop using you for research!
But to be honest, I'm just having fun
spending time with you kids.
You don't mind coming by once
in a while as friends, do you?
Hey. What are you going to do now?
The organization is gone.
I'm obviously going to have
to find another way to live.
Yeah...
Now that the scars on my face are gone,
maybe I'll start up a ramen shop.
The hospitality industry is not for you.
Just put your body to good use.
What are you going to do, Sakurai?
I have an interview at a convenience
store the day after tomorrow.
What? You're going to ask him?
Yes. I'm considering asking Master Reigen
if I can study under him for a while.
Don't. You're really not a people person.
I agree. You're kinda dreary.
The government has determined that
this is the work of
a delusional criminal organization, huh?
I can't believe you turned yourself in
after being defeated by a civilian esper.
It's the truth.
Man, where does that leave us pros?
What's going to happen to my dad?
Under normal circumstances,
he'd be executed.
But there is a chance he'll be kept alive
as a research subject.
Why'd he have to say that to his son?
Well, it's not my call to make,
so I can't say for sure.
P-P-President!
Serizawa.
I never actually considered
you all my comrades.
There's no reason to be worried about me.
Because you lack self-confidence,
others will find you easy to manipulate.
Be careful from now on.
Sho.
I wanted you to see your mother again,
but my pride severed that possibility.
I'm truly sorry.
Don't be.
I see Mom every now and then.
She's always asking me how you're doing.
I wish I could've stopped you
before she found out what you'd become.
When I called her this morning,
she said she'd come see you sometime.
So don't you dare think this is all over.
You still need to get an earful from Mom.
"People need other people," huh?
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
What? It was just a short circuit?
Apparently, a mouse bit into some wires.
Thanks to that, the fire insurance kicked in,
so we get a fresh start at a new office.
But it sure looks bland right now.
Mob, do your thing.
Okay.
Thanks.
The hole in my uniform... I just remembered.
I'd put the broccoli seeds in there.
Broccoli?
The seeds from back the--
Now I see.
Master, you mean that's...
Welp. Let's just forget we ever saw this.
But man, he sure is late...
Oh, there you are.
Come in.
I got lost. I'm very sorry.
Thanks for the other day, Kageyama-kun.
A suit...?
You're going to work here?
Yup. Reigen-san made me
an offer after all that.
I finally figured out who my life belongs to.
Yup. Reigen-san made me an offer after all that.
I finally figured out
who my life belongs to.
I finally figured out who my life belongs to. He
said that there was something that even I could do.
I finally figured out
who my life belongs to.
I finally figured out who my life belongs to. And it's the
least I can do after my organization caused everyone trouble.
And it's the least I can do after
my organization caused everyone trouble.
I'll cover my life's blank canvas with my own colors. And it's
the least I can do after my organization caused everyone trouble.
I'll cover my life's blank canvas
with my own colors.
I'll cover my life's blank canvas with my own colors. We're
here to make a better tomorrow, so this is perfect for you!
We're here to make a better tomorrow,
so this is perfect for you!
You are the only protagonist in the world you color. We're
here to make a better tomorrow, so this is perfect for you!
You are the only protagonist
in the world you color.
You are the only protagonist in the world
you color. Y-Y-Yes, sir! I'll do my best!
You are the only protagonist
in the world you color.
You are the only protagonist in the world you color.
My client will be here soon, but before that...
My client will be here soon,
but before that...
But don't say that you're always alone.
Huh?
But don't say that you're always alone. We're
going to have to do something about that.
But don't say that you're always alone.
Huh?
Whoa, that's amazing.
We will find the answer someday.
He looks so different.
We will find the answer someday. I guess he at least
looks like he can pull off customer service now.
We will find the answer someday.
We will find the answer someday. C-C-Customer service?!
Wh-What should I do when a customer shows up?!
C-C-Customer service?! Wh-What should
I do when a customer shows up?!
So let's never stop walking. C-C-Customer service?!
Wh-What should I do when a customer shows up?!
So let's never stop walking.
What did you do at your last job?
Everyone ends up exchanging breaths with
another. What did you do at your last job?
Everyone ends up exchanging
breaths with another.
Everyone ends up exchanging breaths with another. My orders
were to smack them with my umbrella if I sensed any hostility...
Everyone ends up exchanging
breaths with another.
breaths with another. The hell?
Everyone ends up exchanging
breaths with another.
Everyone ends up exchanging breaths with
another. Yeah, things aren't that different here.
Everyone ends up exchanging
breaths with another.
Everyone ends up exchanging breaths with another.
If there's anything else you don't understand,
If there's anything else
you don't understand,
go ahead and ask your senior there.
Let's just live one second at a time.
Senior?
Let's just live one second at a time. Mob, you
show him the ropes while he's still in training.
Mob, you show him the ropes
while he's still in training.
Huh?
It's a pleasure to work with you,
Kageyama-senpai!
Huh? It's... a pleasure
to work with you, too...
What should I do?
Now I'm getting nervous, too.
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office" What
should I do? Now I'm getting nervous, too.
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
Pardon me.
Oh, hello there! Sorry about the mess.
Please have a seat right over there.
Serizawa, get our guest some tea.
T-Tea? I-I'm sorry,
I've never made tea before...
We're doomed.